// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What Does 'BIPOC' STAND FOR?",
    answer: "Black Indeigenous and People of Color",
    options: [
      "Black Including all People and Characters",
      "Black Indeigenous and People of Color",
      "Between Indviduals, People and Causes",
      "Beans, Icing, Potatos On Cheese"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What Notable Figuire can be Found on The Canadian $10 Bill",
    answer: "Viola Desmond",
    options: [
      "Mairuth Sarfield",
      "Carrie Best",
      "Viola Desmond",
      "Lana Ogilvie",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Rose Fortune was a self appointed ____",
    answer: "Policewoman",
    options: [
      "Government Offical",
      "Policewoman",
      "Secretary",
      "Lawyer",

    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Who started the first Cab company in Toronto?",
    answer: "Thornton Blackburn",
    options: [
      "Austin Clarke",
      "Lieutenant Governor Simcoe",
      "LuLu Anderson",
      "Thornton Blackburn",

    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "When Did Black History Month Start in America, and Canada?",
    answer: "1970 & 1995",
    options: [
      "1970 & 1995",
      "1983 & 1995",
      "1970 & 1993",
      "1983 & 1993",

    ]
  },


     {
     numb: 6,
     question: "Anderson Ruffin Abbot was the first Black Canadian Born to be a licensed ____",
     answer: "Physcian",
     options: [
      "Dermatologist",
      "Dentist",
      "Physcian",
      "Paramedic",

     ]
   },

   {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Who was the first Black Canadian to receive the Victoria Cross",
    answer: "William Hall",
    options: [
      "Geroge Brown",
      "Rev Michael Willis",
      "William Hall",
      "Thornton BlackBurn",

    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What were the secret network of people of the Underground Railroad called",
    answer: "Abolitionists",
    options: [
      "Anthrapologist",
      "Abolitionists",
      "Agololgist",
      "Astrologist",

    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What Does The red in the Pan African Flag represent?",
    answer: "The blood that unites and was shed by all people of African Ancestry",
    options: [
      "The blood that unites and was shed by all people of African Ancestry",
      "The fire that burns within the hearts seeking for liberation for all",
      "The love of the people that are tied together by the representation of the flag",
      "The courage found amongest it's people, united and unwavering",

    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What Month does Black History Month fall on?",
    answer: "February",
    options: [
      "February",
      "July",
      "August",
      "December",

    ]
  },
];